(Leonard:)No, I'm having a moral crisis.
(Sheldon:)Well, if it's of any help, I've read all
the great moral philosophers...
(Sheldon:)...including Dr. Seuss.
Oh, what the hell?
(Leonard:)I'm supposed to go see that
girl from the comic book store, Alice.
(Leonard:)But I don't know if I should, because I'm
going out with Priya, but she's in India.
(Sheldon:)All right.
So the topic at hand is sexual fidelity.
(Sheldon:)Probably won't be relying
on Seuss here.
AIthough One Fish Two Fish
Red Fish Blue Fish...
(Sheldon:)...might be surprisingly applicable.
(Sheldon:)- Go on.
- Well, uh, they say at the end of your life...
(Leonard:)...you regret the stuff you didn't do
more than the stuff that you did.
(Leonard:)And I'm pretty sure Alice is the stuff
I wanna do.
(Sheldon:)You know, the German philosopher
Friedrich Nietzsche...
(Sheldon:)...believed that morality
is just a fiction...
(Sheldon:)...used by the herd of inferior
human beings...